"Mages' lives in danger"?
"Curio Company back after 20 years"?
The Curio Company that was
in The Adventures of Niké?
Were they released...? Or is it a copycat...?
More importantly, have you heard?
Oh my, it sounds like the group calling
themselves the Curio Company has come back.
I thought they'd been
extinguished a long time ago...
I wonder if my husband will be okay...
Will mages be attacked again...?
How frightful...
This is no time to be happy.
I want to avoid anything annoying...
All right! I don't look
anything like a mage now!
I'm just an ordinary, beautiful woman!
Now, time to go sightseeing!
"The Two Apprentices"
I'll hurry up and get this to
the United Magic Association office
and finish up this job!
All I have to do is give them
this small box and get my money.
It's an easy job!
It's a witch!
I wonder what she's doing here...
At a time like this, too...
I feel like people are watching me...
Well, I guess they can't
help it since I'm so cute!
Excuse me...
Excuse me, you...
You cute witch girl over there...
Huh? You're talking to me, right?
That's right, that's right.
Miss Witch, this town has
had a lot of trouble recently.
Especially if you wear clothes like that--
Who knows when someone
will decide to attack you?
Attack me?
Is this town that dangerous?
It is. It's terribly dangerous.
Oh? "Terribly dangerous," huh?
It must be hard, then.
You probably don't know this,
but many mages were attacked here in the past.
The mages were all shaking in their boots...
Hurry it up!
Huh?
I-It's nothing!
And so, in order to survive here,
might I suggest Curio--
I mean, Antique Company's
wonderful self-defense item set?
Hah, I knew it'd be something like that.
I turn down all hard sells, so--
Hey, wait--
Um, sorry, I couldn't steal the box...
Useless, as usual.
Forget it.
Change of plan.
We just have to get that small box open.
Let's see... The association's this way, right?
O-Oh, no! Am I going to die?
Quiet! This town is dangerous!
Mina? Long time no see.
Um, what are you doing here, Mina?
I'm here on an undercover
investigation for the association.
There are some people up to no good...
I haven't infiltrated them, yet, though.
Up to no good?
What are you doing here, Big Sis?
I'm here for work, too.
Work. For the association.
Of all things, work for the association?
To deliver this.
What is it?
Dunno.
I haven't heard anything
from the association, though...
Anyway, let's go to my lodgings for now.
Oh, I'm just going to deliver this.
I don't want to trouble you,
so I'll just stay at an inn.
Don't worry about me!
Really?
If you sigh, happiness escapes, you know.
That cafe...
Could it be the place where Foula
met up with the Curio Company boss?
Wow!
I wonder which seat Foula sat in...
She should be fine.
You sure?
She looks dumb,
so I'm sure she'd just open that box
without thinking about anything.
Huh?
Listen.
You don't have to do anything, Big Sis.
"Big Sis"? Who?
Where am I? I thought
I was in front of the cafe....
Those guys are planning to
attack all the stores in town,
from jewelry shops to
weapons sellers to general stores.
This... isn't a dream?
Are you listening, Big Sis?
Um, excuse me. Who are you? I--
You don't have to joke around like that.
This isn't a joke, though...
Anyway, my voice seems...
Huh?
Big Sis...?
Big Sis, what are you--
Poisonous gas or something?
Oh, I was so surprised by our
fateful meeting that I forgot to breathe!
Miss Elaina!
Um... Are you all right?
Big... Sis...
Are you feeling unwell somewhere? Your stomach?
Do you have a fever? Or nausea?
Don't touch me!
Ow...
U-Um...
Big Sis...
So cute.
I love you.
Big Sis, I've loved you for a long time...
It's strange, right?
--But for a long time, you've been
the only thing I could think about.
--Wai--
--But for a long time, you've been
the only thing I could think about.
--Wai--
--Even though you're my big sister,
you follow me, your little sister,
around like a dog, relying on me.
You're a pitiful, unreliable big sister,
but oh, you're so, so, so cute!
So, so, so, so cute, I can't stand it!
Jeez! I don't need anything
other than you in my life!
I'm sorry I always treat
you coldly despite that.
But I really love you so much.
I'm sorry I couldn't be honest with my feelings.
I actually love you so much
I could eat you up! I love, love, love, love,
love, love, love, love, love you!
So please...
With me--
Oof.
Jeez, what's going on...?
--Wait!
--I love you!
--Don't come here!
--You're acting weird!
--Calm down!
I adore you!
The one I love is your little brother!
--I love you! I love you so much!
--Your feelings are enough!
--Don't come near me!
--Oh, I love you! Please go out with me!
--Wait a minute!
--What's the matter? You seem scary!
--Don't come near me!
--Oh, I love you! Please go out with me!
--Wait a minute!
--What's the matter? You seem scary!
This is crazy.
It's probably--no, it's without
a doubt--because I opened the box.
I love--
This voice...
--No!
--Come on!
You really are cute. You're so
cute no matter how I look at you.
Th-That appearance...
Love...
That's me no matter how you look at it.
Saya...?
Huh?
Me?
Huh?!
Huh? What's going on?
Nothing is making sense! Explain yourself, Saya!
I don't know what's going on, either!
Before I knew it, I had turned
into such a cute Miss Elaina.
Besides, I don't know why the rest of
the town has ended up like this, either!
Oh, that part's fine. I know why that happened.
Huh?
By the way, about why we've switched bodies...
Wait, what do you mean you know
why the town ended up like this?
Let's leave that aside for now.
I should've had a box with me...
What happened to it?
It contained something dangerous
and that should never be opened.
Hey, wait!
This way!
Don't tell me you opened it?
Well...
Just a little.
Hey! What are you doing? Jeez!
There's no way anything good would
come of opening something like that!
My little sister didn't stop you?!
Little sister?
Wasn't she there?
A strangely sexy girl with black hair?
Oh, there was...
Your eyes are dead.
You sisters are really similar.
What? Really? No, we're not!
Will you please not make
that expression with my face?
What expression?
Oh, I love you!
Please get away from the window.
Don't wanna! I wanna stay
with you for the rest of my life!
Our first priority right now should
be to get this city back to normal.
No, not "our"--my first priority.
It was my fault to begin with.
Then, since I'm you right now,
we can say I should do it, too, right?
I'm grateful, but please
get away from the window.
But what was inside that box, anyway?
More of a curse than magic.
Probably something like a love potion?
So someone switched us and
then made you open it, or something?
Would someone really make such a sloppy plan?
You're right. That's too sloppy.
As the boss planned,
a witch nonchalantly brought the
small box that was confiscated in the past
believing it was a job for
the United Magic Association.
I couldn't steal the box from the witch,
but when we switched
the witch with a foolish girl,
the girl opened the box for us!
Thanks to that, the whole town is in chaos!
Now, go steal! The effect
of the smoke won't last for long!
All of you of the revived Curio Company!
Steal as much as you can right now!
Speaking of which,
your sister said something about
some people attacking the stores...
Those people are...
The Curio Company has been revived, huh?
What's the Curio Company?
In the book, The Adventures of Niké--
Oh, I've never read it before.
Then, never mind.
Anyway, it's pretty sloppy, but
all the mysteries have been solved.
Um, uh, I'm sorry for getting carried away...
No, no, it's fine.
As long as you tell us where
the leader of the Curio Company is.
And so, we headed to the place the nice man
told us about, where the leader was.
What? But it was the perfect plan!
No, it was extremely sloppy.
But, Miss Elaina, you were
completely tricked, right?
Even so, I never thought
I'd also be able to capture
the Curio Company boss
from The Adventures of Niké.
Damn.
Oh, right, we want you to
put our bodies back to normal.
I'm totally fine staying like this, though.
We want you to put our bodies back to normal.
I-I can't do it right away...
Huh?
Th-They should go back in about a day...
There's no mistake?
Sniff...
However!
However?
Don't think that you've won!
There are a lot of us.
Dozens more than the ones you caught!
Right about now, the chaos
in town should be multiplying,
with everyone stealing
what they can and escaping!
Too bad! We win!
Wh-What should we do?
All we can do is split up and search, right?
No, there's no need.
Huh?!
Miss Fran?!
T-Teach?!
"Teach"? You mean Sheila?
Long time no see,
fanged leader of the Curio Company.
Huh?
You're that apprentice witch from that time?
"From that time"?
Oh my, your fangs are now... I'm sorry.
Huh? Huh?
Don't worry about the Curio Company
guys going crazy outside.
We've already taken care of all of them!
Too bad. You lost again.
"Again"...?
Now, what do we need to do to
get the townspeople back to normal?
Why is she unconscious?
And now, the townspeople are back to normal.
It was actually pretty easy.
Why is she unconscious?
About that box...
Was it brought from an island
far beyond the horizon?
That's right.
As expected of Miss Elaina! You sure know a lot!
Were we also switched
because of an item from that island?
When you see a person you kind of like,
you can't act normal anymore,
and when you see someone
you really like, you become hopeless.
That's the curse on that smoke.
I see.
Who cares?
Miss Elaina.
Yes?
I have heard about you from my sister.
I heard that you taught
her magic after I left her,
and that you found each
other again in another country.
She sounded so happy when she talked about it.
Um, why did you leave Saya in the Land of Mages?
She was pretty depressed, you know.
Oh, that's because I wanted to start
her training as a witch right away,
so I forced her to go back to her homeland.
You did, Sheila?
I'm Mina's teacher, too.
You didn't know?
No, I didn't.
Saya has a tendency to depend on people, right?
It didn't seem like it would be good
for either of them to always be together.
I see. I thought for sure it was
because Mina was tired of Saya
and left her behind to go home.
Actually, Mina wouldn't let me hear
the end of it when she got back.
She said stuff like
"Why did you make me leave my sister?"
and "I'll never forgive you!"
and "I'll curse you my whole life!"
Oh? Mina said that?
Well, that's unexpected--
Actually, based on what happened
yesterday, it's not unexpected at all.
Yesterday?
This makes it hard to tell who
was depending on whom, huh?
P-Please stop talking about it already!
No! I don't wanna! I don't wanna go home!
I wanna stay with Miss Elaina!
Stop whining.
There's work to do, so we're leaving now.
Then, I'll quit!
Then how will you eat?
I'll have Miss Elaina make me her bride.
Sorry, no.
You heard her.
Big Sis, give it up--
She's looking at me hostilely.
Really hostilely...
See ya.
Yes, see you in a year.
I don't wanna...
No... Miss Elaina!
You are very loved.
Yeah, I guess so.
Hey, Elaina.
Yes?
You've realized, right?
Realized what?
Who my teacher was.
Your teacher? Who...?
It looks like you still can't be honest
with yourself about the important things.
I don't have any problems the way I am.
It wouldn't hurt to fix
that part of yourself, though.
I still want to keep traveling,
and I still want to visit lots of countries.
I'll leisurely do the things I want to do.
If I realize...
I feel like my days of
traveling freely will be over.
No matter who has influenced you,
or whether or not you've realized who that is,
I don't think anything will change, though.
You really think so?
I do. Did you know?
My teacher always seemed
like she acted in a calculating way,
but she was actually pretty laid-back.
Really?
And you are also pretty laid-back.
Really?!
So I don't think you need
to care about the small things.
But one of these days, please go back home.
One of these days.
Don't forget.
We're always thinking about you.
We'll always love you.
Me, too...
I love you, Miss Fran. And everyone...
Take care!
There are five volumes
in The Adventures of Niké.
I don't want my story to end in five volumes.
That's why--
In the country where Miss Fran and Sheila
were able to be honest with each other,
I took a new step forward.
I want to keep being just the Ashen Witch--
Just an ordinary traveler.